CV last update: 15/09/2023



Roman Ivanov

Certified Software Developer Specializing in Web Development



§ 5123161
☐ roman.ivanov.dev@gmail.com
☐ https://justenough1.github.io

Summary

I am a certified software developer with almost a year of experience in web development and design. My proficiency in programming languages and problem-solving techniques was acquired through a four-year vocational school education. I am committed to continuous growth and development, and to the creation of innovative websites and software products.

Work experience

Web developer (internship)

EDUKAD SILLAMÄE NOORED - ESN MTÜ / Estonia

www.molodoi.ee

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023 (6 m)

Culture / Entertainment / Recreation

- Played an important role in the development, testing and improvement of the website, with a focus on both functionality and design.
- Participated in team meetings and brainstorming sessions to promote collaboration and achieving the goals of the project.
- Assisted in identifying and resolving issues and errors to ensure a positive user experience.

Web developer (internship)

Sillamäe Sadam AS / Estonia

www.silport.ee

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022 (4 m)

Transportation / Logistics

- Assisted in identifying and resolving errors on the website to ensure a positive user experience.
- Provided clear and concise reports on bugs, testing results, and solutions to the internship supervisor.

Education

Ida-Virumaa Vocational Education Center (Estonia, Vocational education)

Software developer

2019 - 2023

Sillamäe Vanalinna School (Estonia, Elementary education)

2011 - 2019

Language skills

Language Listening Reading Communication Presentation Writing

Russian (Language of communication)

English B2 ? B2 ? B2 ? B2 ?

Levels: A1/A2 - Basic user; B1/B2 - Independent user; C1/C2 - Proficient user

Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

Computer skills

Programming languages

Expert JavaScript, Typescript

Advanced SQL, Python, Java

Intermediate C#

Other

Expert HTML / CSS, Bootstrap, React.JS, Tailwind CSS, WordPress

Advanced Socket.IO, Next.JS, MySQL

Intermediate MongoDB

Webdesign software

Expert Figma

Office software

Expert Visual Studio Code, PhpMyAdmin

Advanced GitHub, Atlassian Jira, Postman, NetBeans

Intermediate AWS

Desired position

Information Technology

Front-end developer, Software developer, Web developer, Back-end developer, Full-Stack Developer

Work type

Employee, Contract worker

Working time

Full-time, Part-time, Freelance

Locations

Tallinn, Tartu, Pärnu, Narva, Kohtla Järve / Jõhvi

Countries

Europe

Additional info

In my free time, I prefer to spend time with my loved ones or playing the guitar. I also enjoy cycling and occasionally go for rides in the city or nearby areas.

I value good relationships with colleagues and strive to create a positive and productive work atmosphere. My main qualities are responsibility and a commitment to delivering high-quality work.